<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Benobi.one</title>
    <link>https://benobi.one/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Benobi.one</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://benobi.one/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Gratitude</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/posts/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/posts/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for visiting. This is my first post. I belive that we should always begin new things with gratitude.
I am grateful for all of the various experiences I have had and the many apps and projects I have worked on over since 2013. I can&amp;rsquo;t believe the project list here covers only 7 years!
I am grateful for this site and domain which my dear friend Crystal Rose inspired me to put together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Benobi</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/about/</guid>
      <description>About the name Benobi was a nickname given to me by my girlfriend back in 2016 - which really stuck because of my awareness and my calm, zen-like approach to problem solving. I was doing a lot of self-work during the 2015-2016 time period. The training has paid off&amp;hellip; as a wise person once said, the best investment is to invest in ourselves.
 About this site This is a site to showcase some of the things I have been working on for the past few years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/contact/</guid>
      <description>Want to chat? Feel free to Tweet at me any time or reach me on EOS Chat @benmakesense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/projects/</guid>
      <description>2019 - Sense (EOS) Chat  I joined as the CTO of Sense Chat - a decentralized messaging app built on the EOS blockchain. The beta app is live on the Google Play and Apple App Store.
EOS Chat leverages blockchain for accounts, authentication, encryption, and allows users to send tokens to one another with no middle man. It does not require a phone number to use, therefore it is entirely pseudonymous.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>