<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Benobi.one</title>
    <link>https://benobi.one/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Benobi.one</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 22:40:30 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://benobi.one/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a Simple iOS App: Retro Ping App</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/posts/building_retro_ping/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 22:40:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/posts/building_retro_ping/</guid>
      <description>I built a mobile app this weekend in Swift. I&amp;rsquo;m very happy with the end product and I have already tested it out with a few friends.
I wanted to discuss a step-by-step process that I used for building it along with some gotchas and learnings.
Here are the 15 steps I took to create this app:
 Spec Wire Design Code Function Test Functions on Physical Device Code style Test Refine Submit App to Testflight Work on App Store Elements Test App on Testflight (various devices) Refine App Test App Again Submit App to Apple App Review Launch  I knew I wanted to build a simple app with a simple purpose: measure latency and simply say if the connection is &amp;ldquo;good&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;bad&amp;rdquo; based on the latency of the phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gardening and Building Product</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/posts/gardening_apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 13:20:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/posts/gardening_apps/</guid>
      <description>I have been doing some gardening during our COVID-19 quarantine and I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about how there are similarities between building a product and growing a garden.
My mom loves gardening. One of her favorite movies, &amp;ldquo;Being There&amp;rdquo; is about a simple man &amp;ldquo;Chauncey Gardiner&amp;rdquo; who has spent his entire life in the garden. Since Chauncey has only known the garden his whole life, that is the only way he understands the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Defending the Product Roadmap</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/posts/feature_creep/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 14:46:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/posts/feature_creep/</guid>
      <description>Protecting developers from an increasing scope of work before the initial agreed-upon work is completed is one of the skills of a good tech lead / project developer.
Of course, it&amp;rsquo;s a complicated isuse in a way because ideation can be the ultimate creator and killer of products.
“It would be cool if this broom absorbed water&amp;hellip;” - A mop is born. “It would be cool if this mop also had a disco light.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animated GIFs in Swift Xcode</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/posts/swift_gifs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 02:48:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/posts/swift_gifs/</guid>
      <description>Bye StackOverflow Gone are the days of Stack Overflow; long live YouTube coding tutorials. My Dad used to have a library of home improvement books. It was a set of over 40 color coded books covering every topic from plumbing to roofing to electrical. The books were not that easy to follow either&amp;hellip; diagrams are often not as good as seeing someone do whatever it is you are trying to do in a video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JAMstack Serverless Hugo Deployment</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/posts/hugo_deployment_to_github/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 02:27:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/posts/hugo_deployment_to_github/</guid>
      <description>This site is built on Hugo which is really fast and easy to work with - even if you are only a basic developer. Here is how I setup my Hugo deployments. It&amp;rsquo;s actually really simple and it will help you save a lot of time updating your site.
Setup vscode to play nicely with Hugo These will help you to see your syntax and build your site from vscode directly using the command pallete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Killer Apps</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/posts/killer-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/posts/killer-apps/</guid>
      <description>In consumer tech products, the holy grail is often referred to as the &amp;ldquo;killer app.&amp;rdquo; Of course, in this phrase &amp;ldquo;killer&amp;rdquo; means that an app will break the mold and have hockey-stick levels of adoption and user activity. This leads many to ponder the question&amp;hellip;
What is the formula for a killer app? Well, there is a man who wrote a formula. I am grateful to have spent some time with Eyal Herzog over the past two years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gratitude</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/posts/gratitude/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/posts/gratitude/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for visiting. This is my first post. I belive that we should always begin new things with gratitude.
I am grateful for all of the various experiences I have had and the many apps and projects I have worked on since 2013. I can&amp;rsquo;t believe the project list here covers only 7 years!
I am grateful for this site and domain which my dear friend Crystal Rose inspired me to put together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Benobi</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/about/</guid>
      <description>Curiousity is an art form itself. I&amp;rsquo;ve always been a very curious person. I love to learn about people and I love to learn new tricks. My main interests are: internet philosophy, blockchain, building consumer apps, linux \ web security, air quality, dogs, chess, and astrology.
Before going full-force into building products in 2017, I ran a technology consulting company that I started back in college. The consulting company took me on many adventures and introduced me to many great people - it&amp;rsquo;s still profitable and being run by my business partner today!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/contact/</guid>
      <description>Want to chat? Feel free to Tweet at me any time or reach me on EOS Chat @benmakesense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/projects/</guid>
      <description>This is a list of the major projects I have worked on since 2013. Until Sense Chat, all of my projects were 100% self-funded.
 2019 - Sense (EOS) Chat  I joined as the CTO of Sense Chat - a decentralized messaging app built on the EOS blockchain. The beta app is live on the Google Play and Apple App Store.
EOS Chat leverages blockchain for accounts, authentication, encryption, and allows users to send tokens to one another with no middle man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web resources and great projects</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/resources/</guid>
      <description>This is a list of resources that I find useful / interesting.
 Defend Freedom Online  JP Barlow is one of the internet&amp;rsquo;s greatest heroes. The Declaration of the Independence of Cyberspace is a really special document to me. I think I teared up a little bit when I first read it. There are many people who do not feel at home where they are physically. Ultimately, what makes the internet beatiful is a collection of connections between the ideas of people.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>