<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Benobi.one</title>
    <link>https://benobi.one/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Benobi.one</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 02:27:29 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://benobi.one/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>JAMstack Hugo Deployment to Github and Netlify</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/posts/hugo_deployment_to_github/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 02:27:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/posts/hugo_deployment_to_github/</guid>
      <description>This site is built on Hugo which is really fast and easy to work with - even if you are only a basic developer. Here is how I setup my Hugo deployments. It&amp;rsquo;s actually really simple and it will help you save a lot of time updating your site.
Setup vscode to play nicely with Hugo These will help you to see your syntax and build your site from vscode directly using the command pallete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Killer Apps</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/posts/killer-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/posts/killer-apps/</guid>
      <description>In consumer tech products, the holy grail is often referred to as the &amp;ldquo;killer app.&amp;rdquo; Of course, in this phrase &amp;ldquo;killer&amp;rdquo; means that an app will break the mold and have hockey-stick levels of adoption and user activity. This leads many to ponder the question&amp;hellip;
What is the formula for a killer app? Well, there is a man who wrote a formula. I am grateful to have spent some time with Eyal Herzog over the past two years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gratitude</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/posts/gratitude/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/posts/gratitude/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for visiting. This is my first post. I belive that we should always begin new things with gratitude.
I am grateful for all of the various experiences I have had and the many apps and projects I have worked on since 2013. I can&amp;rsquo;t believe the project list here covers only 7 years!
I am grateful for this site and domain which my dear friend Crystal Rose inspired me to put together.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>