<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Benobi.one</title>
    <link>https://benobi.one/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Benobi.one</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 22:21:48 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://benobi.one/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Defining Moments</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/posts/defining_moments/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 22:21:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/posts/defining_moments/</guid>
      <description>COVID-19 is a defining moment for our lives and for the world. For the next unknown months or years - there is a default level of hardship in the world than before. In a way, this is our first global problem. It&amp;rsquo;s a problem for all humans, this little virus.
What exactly will this moment define?
The COVID-19 pandemic - or as should have been called SARS-CoV-2 - is going to leave the world a very different place than it was before the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID App in Flutter</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/posts/covid_app_idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 23:39:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/posts/covid_app_idea/</guid>
      <description>While I am waiting to hear from Apple about whether or not they will allow me to update Retro Ping, I was thinking about building another really simple app. This app would simply allow people to check how many COVID-19 cases there are near them.
The app would be pretty simple. I found a bunch of data on Github that is updated daily into CSV files. I could simply download those and transform them into a JSON, then write some simple logic to create an API where the mobile app can get latitude and longitude - send that data to the backend and get back the number of cases for that region.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attending Virtual Events</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/posts/oculus_quest_new_view/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 23:30:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/posts/oculus_quest_new_view/</guid>
      <description>I rentered virtual reality this weekend when a new Oculus Quest arrived in my yard. A very good friend of mine sent it to me as a gift and I&amp;rsquo;m really excited to dig back into VR. A few years ago, when I got my HTC Vive - there were not really that many interesting games or things to do. Wow, VR has grown a lot in a short amount of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Importance of Writing Good Spec Docs</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/posts/writing_spec_docs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 14:54:45 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/posts/writing_spec_docs/</guid>
      <description>Writing spec documents is an important aspect of building a product. As I wrote about in my post about building a simple iOS app, even if I am building an app myself - I start with a specification document. it&amp;rsquo;s very useful as a tool to think through all of my product interactions and explain how they will work. If I cannot explain it very simply, then I will not be able to build it - neither will anyone else!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TikTok Timing and Sharability</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/posts/tiktok_is_vine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 15:24:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/posts/tiktok_is_vine/</guid>
      <description>Despite the great gap that the media likes to paint between the US and China, the Beijing-based TikTok app has been connecting users from both countries - and just about everywhere in-between. TikTok has taken over.
But what about this video platform makes it so addictive and fun?
It definitely meets all 3 of the killer app criteria in the formula for killer apps I wrote about last week: low cost of failure, high value of success, and free marketing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Krueger&#39;s 3 Key Ingredients for a Killer App</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/posts/killer_apps_mvp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:34:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/posts/killer_apps_mvp/</guid>
      <description>Coming back to the killer apps topic I wrote about last week, I wanted to talk a little bit about what I have learned from friend and mentor of mine, Fred Kreuger. Fred is a CEO and a product guy which is an amazing combination. He has had 9/10 wins for his investors and has run a publicly traded company. Fred earned a PhD in Math from Stanford where he wrote a dissertation titled D-arrangements and Random Polyhedra which later became several classes at Stanford and informed some of the math used in modern cryptography.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perspective on App Store Reviews</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/posts/apple_app_store_reviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 00:11:06 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/posts/apple_app_store_reviews/</guid>
      <description>Super thankful today for all of the reviews I have gotten. It looks like I am now up to 52 &amp;ldquo;5 Star&amp;rdquo; reviews on the Apple App Store!!! As I wrote about a few days ago, my app was approved, and then the first update was rejected within 24 hours for the app being so simple. I want to give a big thanks to everyone who downloaded the app and also wrote reviews.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lightning fast performance with JAMstack</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/posts/jamstack_speed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 10:52:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/posts/jamstack_speed/</guid>
      <description>This website has been built with serverless architecture using JAMstack.
The speed of this architecture is really unparalleled. The trick is that I am delivering static content on CDNs.
The entire source code for this site is hosted on GitHub. I have written a previous post about building this site.
Blazing Speed Take a look at the blazing performance of https://benobi.one - the site usually gets a score of 95-100 in terms of speed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rejection is the Beginning of Negotiation</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/posts/app_store_rejection/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 22:46:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/posts/app_store_rejection/</guid>
      <description>There are dozens of reasons you might get rejected by the Apple App Review Team - your metadata might have issues, your screenshots might not have the correct placement of the WiFi or battery symbols, or they might just think your app is boring! I have personally had apps rejected and I have also helped friends navigate app rejections. If your app gets rejected, do not give up! Depending on the reviewer, you might get different results for the same app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a Simple iOS App: Retro Ping App</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/posts/building_retro_ping/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 22:40:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/posts/building_retro_ping/</guid>
      <description>I built a mobile app this weekend in Swift. I&amp;rsquo;m very happy with the end product and I have already tested it out with a few friends.
I wanted to discuss a step-by-step process that I used for building it along with some gotchas and learnings.
Here are the 15 steps I took to create this app:
 Spec Wire Design Code Function Test Functions on Physical Device Code style Test Refine Submit App to Testflight Work on App Store Elements Test App on Testflight (various devices) Refine App Test App Again Submit App to Apple App Review Launch  I knew I wanted to build a simple app with a simple purpose: measure latency and simply say if the connection is &amp;ldquo;good&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;bad&amp;rdquo; based on the latency of the phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gardening and Building Product</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/posts/gardening_apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 13:20:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/posts/gardening_apps/</guid>
      <description>I have been doing some gardening during our COVID-19 quarantine and I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about how there are similarities between building a product and growing a garden.
My mom loves gardening. One of her favorite movies, &amp;ldquo;Being There&amp;rdquo; is about a simple man &amp;ldquo;Chauncey Gardiner&amp;rdquo; who has spent his entire life in the garden. Since Chauncey has only known the garden his whole life, that is the only way he understands the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Defending the Product Roadmap</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/posts/feature_creep/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 14:46:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/posts/feature_creep/</guid>
      <description>Protecting developers from an increasing scope of work before the initial agreed-upon work is completed is one of the skills of a good tech lead / project developer.
Of course, it&amp;rsquo;s a complicated isuse in a way because ideation can be the ultimate creator and killer of products.
“It would be cool if this broom absorbed water&amp;hellip;” - A mop is born. “It would be cool if this mop also had a disco light.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animated GIFs in Swift Xcode</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/posts/swift_gifs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 02:48:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/posts/swift_gifs/</guid>
      <description>Bye StackOverflow Gone are the days of Stack Overflow; long live YouTube coding tutorials. My Dad used to have a library of home improvement books. It was a set of over 40 color coded books covering every topic from plumbing to roofing to electrical. The books were not that easy to follow either&amp;hellip; diagrams are often not as good as seeing someone do whatever it is you are trying to do in a video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JAMstack Serverless Hugo Deployment</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/posts/hugo_deployment_to_github/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 02:27:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/posts/hugo_deployment_to_github/</guid>
      <description>This site is built on Hugo which is really fast and easy to work with - even if you are only a basic developer. Here is how I setup my Hugo deployments. It&amp;rsquo;s actually really simple and it will help you save a lot of time updating your site.
Setup vscode to play nicely with Hugo These will help you to see your syntax and build your site from vscode directly using the command pallete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Killer Apps</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/posts/killer-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/posts/killer-apps/</guid>
      <description>In consumer tech products, the holy grail is often referred to as the &amp;ldquo;killer app.&amp;rdquo; Of course, in this phrase &amp;ldquo;killer&amp;rdquo; means that an app will break the mold and have hockey-stick levels of adoption and user activity. This leads many to ponder the question&amp;hellip;
What is the formula for a killer app Well, there is a man who wrote a formula. I am grateful to have spent some time with Eyal Herzog over the past two years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gratitude</title>
      <link>https://benobi.one/posts/gratitude/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benobi.one/posts/gratitude/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for visiting This is my first post. I belive that we should always begin new things with gratitude.
I am grateful for all of the various experiences I have had and the many apps and projects I have worked on since 2013. I can&amp;rsquo;t believe the project list here covers only 7 years!
I am grateful for this site and domain which my dear friend Crystal Rose inspired me to put together.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>